Guide to the Ernesto Galarza Papers, 1936-1984
Department of Special Collections
- Subject files, 1923-1978, Series 4
  - Subseries C: Braceros (Policy), 1943-1967
    - U.S. Dept. of Labor, Bureau of Employment Security, miscellany, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Dept. of Labor, Bureau of Employment Security, report to U.S. House of Representatives on bracero program, 1956-1962 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Dept. of Labor, Bureau of Employment Security, staff manual, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Dept. of Labor, Bureau of Employment Security, statistics on foreign and domestic farm labor, 1950-1956, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Dept. of State, correspondence, news releases, 1944-1954 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - U.S.-Mexican governments, agreements relating to importation of braceros, 1937-1956 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Wartime U.S. government agencies, 1942-1945, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - California, Governor's Committee to Survey the Agricultural Labor Resources of the San Joaquin Valley, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - California, Senate Fact Finding Committee on Labor and Welfare (Cobey Committee), legislative testimony, 1950-1964 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - California, Senate Fact Finding Committee on Labor and Welfare (Cobey Committee), notes, newsclippings, 1952-1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Caribbean/West Indian contract laborers, 1948-1959 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Central Valley Project, 1946-1971 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Central Valley Project, newsclippings, 1944-1961 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Contractors, correspondence, 1950-1961 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Contractors, "Farm Labor Contractors in California," ca. 1948 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Contractors, notes and miscellany, 1950-1959 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Subseries D: Court Cases, 1950-1960
    - Anti-noise ordinances, 1950-1951 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Arismendi Arismendi, Ezequiel, v. Elvira Ruiz, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Berverdor, Inc., 1958 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - D'Arrigo Brothers, 1959-1960 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Driscoll-Shuben, 1958-1960 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Eagan, Charles, appeal of suspension from California Department of Employment, 1957-1959 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Ferry-Morse Seed Company, 1958-1960 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Garcia Carbajal, Isabel, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Renner, William, dismissal from U.S. Dept. of Labor, correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Renner, William, employment records, 1956-1958 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Renner, William, Galarza's notes, newsclippings, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Renner, William, Renner's notes, payroll data, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Renner, William, reports, miscellany, Jan.-Sept., 1957 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Renner, William, reports, miscellany, Oct., 1957-Jan., 1958 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Schenley Industries, Inc., 1952 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Stokeley-Van Camp, Inc., correspondence, notes, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Stokeley-Van Camp, miscellany, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Twistems case, correspondence, notes, 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Twistems case, statements, reports, miscellany, 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Venegas-Driscoll Associates, notes, wage sheets, 1956-1958 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Venegas-Driscoll Associates, production records (picker), 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Venegas-Driscoll Associates, production records (picker), (Venegas), 1956-1958 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Subseries E: Crops, 1947-1966
    - Asparagus, marketing orders, reports, 1948-1961 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Asparagus, newsclippings, 1949-1962 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Asparagus, notes, 1948-1960 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Citrus fruit, 1948-1961 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Cotton, California Planting Cottonseed Distributors, Inc., correspondence, 1951-1960 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Cotton, California Planting Cottonseed Distributors, reports, notes, 1949-1960 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Cotton, correspondence, notes, reports, 1947-1950 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Cotton, market reports, 1949-1962 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Cotton, mechanization, reports, 1947-1952 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Cotton, mechanization, newsclippings, 1948-1961 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Cotton, NFLU Strike, correspondence, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Cotton, NFLU Strike, newsclippings, 1949-1950 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Cotton, NFLU Strike, notes, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Cotton, NFLU Strike, press releases, bulletins, 1949-1950 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Cotton, wages, 1949-1950 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Grapes, 1949-1961 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Mechanization, newsclippings, 1949-1964 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Miscellany, 1948-1962 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Peaches, marketing orders, newsletters, notes, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Peaches, newsclippings, 1948-1961 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Potatoes, 1950-1961 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Production data, 1947-1962 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Prunes, 1948-1959 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Statistics, newsclippings, 1948-1960 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Strawberries, 1954-1959 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Sugar beets, 1949-1960 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Tomatoes, 1951-1965 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Tomatoes, newsclippings, 1947-1966 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Subseries F: DiGiorgio Fruit Corporation, 1947-1970
    - Annual report, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - California State Senate Committee on Un-American Activities, "Statements Given Before Hon. Hugh M. Burns, Vice-Chairman," Jan., 1948 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Citizens Committee on the DiGiorgio Strike, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - "A Community Aroused," 1947 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Congressional Record, 1948-1950 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Legal documents, 1942-1947 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Legal documents, 1948-1949 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Legal documents, 1950-1951 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Newsclippings, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Newsclippings, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Newsclippings, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Newsclippings, 1950-1959 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings, 1960-1970 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Newsletter, 1947-1964 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Notes, ca. 1947-1949 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - "Poverty in the Valley of Plenty," n.d. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Press releases, 1947-1950 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Rosters of strikers, strikebreakers, contributors, ca. 1948 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Statements and reports, 1948, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Strike bulletins, ca. Sept., 1947-Aug., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Strike chronologies, 1948-1949 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Strike songs (lyrics only), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Transcripts of forum and radio program, 1949, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - U.S. House of Representatives, Committee on Education and Labor, Special Investigating Sub-committee Number One, "Investigation of Labor Management," Bakersfield, Nov., 1949 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - U.S. House of Representatives, Committee on Education and Labor, Special Investigating Sub-committee Number One, "Memorandum-Brief on the DiGiorgio Strike and Conditions Among the Agricultural Workers of California," Nov., 1949 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - U.S. House of Representatives, Committee on Education and Labor,Special Sub-committee on Labor Management Relations Act, hearings on National Labor Relations Act of 1949 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Subseries G: DiGiorgio Fruit Corporation--Court Cases 1949-1969
    - DiGiorgio v. AFL-CIO, et. al. (10522, California Court of Appeals, Third District, San Francisco), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - DiGiorgio v. AFL-CIO, (72535, California Superior Court, San Joaquin Co.), deposition, portion of proceedings, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - DiGiorgio v. AFL-CIO, legal documents, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - DiGiorgio v. Cascade Labor News (32363, California Superior Court, Shasta Co.), correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - DiGiorgio v. Cascade Labor News (32363, California Superior Court, Shasta Co.), legal documents, 1964-1968 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - DiGiorgio v. Flannery, et. al. (566888, California Superior Court, Los Angeles Co.), deposition, 1949-1950 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - DiGiorgio v. Monterey Bay Labor News (57404, California Superior Court, Monterey Co.), deposition, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - DiGiorgio v. Monterey Bay Labor News (57404, California Superior Court, Monterey Co.), legal documents, 1964-1968 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - DiGiorgio v. Norman Smith, et. al. (71841, California Superior Court, San Joaquin Co.), correspondence, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - DiGiorgio v. Norman Smith, et. al. (71841, California Superior Court, San Joaquin Co.), legal documents, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - DiGiorgio v. Norman Smith, et. al. (71841, California Superior Court, San Joaquin Co.), newsclippings, 1961-1964 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - DiGiorgio v. Union Gazette, et. al. (544554, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - DiGiorgio v. Union Gazette, et. al. (544554, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), depositions, 1964-1966 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - DiGiorgio v. Union Gazette, et. al. (544554, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), legal documents, 1964-1968 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - DiGiorgio v. United Packinghouse Workers of America (72635, California Superior Court, San Joaquin Co.), 1961 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (740, California Court of Appeals, Fifth District, Fresno), briefs, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (740, California Court of Appeals, Fifth District, Fresno), clerk's transcript on appeal, Aug. 2, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (740, California Court of Appeals, Fifth District, Fresno), correspondence, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (740, California Court of Appeals, Fifth District, Fresno), reporter's transcript on appeal, vol. I, Mar., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (740, California Court of Appeals, Fifth District, Fresno), reporter's transcript on appeal, vol. II, Mar., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (740, California Court of Appeals, Fifth District, Fresno), reporter's transcript on appeal, vol. III, Mar., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (740, California Court of Appeals, Fifth District, Fresno), reporter's transcript on appeal, vol. IV, Mar., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (122891, California Superior Court, Fresno Co.), corporate records, 1956-1957 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (122891, California Superior Court, Fresno Co.), correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (122891, California Superior Court, Fresno Co.), deposition, George Ballis, July 25, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (122891, California Superior Court, Fresno Co.), deposition, Jeff Boehm, Oct. 28, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (122891, California Superior Court, Fresno Co.), deposition, Charles S. Gubser, Dec. 28, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (122891, California Superior Court, Fresno Co.), deposition, Loyd Myers, July 14, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (122891, California Superior Court, Fresno Co.), deposition, Robert M. Perkins, July 14, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (122891, California Superior Court, Fresno Co.), deposition, Wallace E. Sedgwick, July 7, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (122891, California Superior Court, Fresno Co.), deposition, Tom Steed, Sept. 13, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - DiGiorgio v. Valley Labor Citizen (122891, California Superior Court, Fresno Co.), legal documents, 1964-1969 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Francis v. Olympic Press, et. al. (104034, California Superior Court, San Mateo County), 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (84258, California Superior Court, Kern Co.), 1962 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), citations, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), concordance, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), citations, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), citations, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), citations, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), citations, 1965-1968 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), defendant's proposed jury instructions, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Glenn Brockway, Dec. 20, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, William R. Callan, Sept. 18, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Russell Charles Derrickson, Apr.29, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Robert DiGiorgio, Dec. 9, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Malcolm T. Dungan, Nov. 7, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Ernesto Galarza, Dec. 27, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Edward F. Hayes, Jan. 22, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Louis F. Krainock, Apr. 19, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Richard Nixon, Jan. 7, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Alfred J. Norton, Feb. 27, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Albert O'Dea, Nov. 30, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Ralph R. Roberts, Apr. 29, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Bruce W. Sanborn, Jr., Nov. 10 and Dec. 2, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Tom Steed, Apr. 30, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), deposition, Thomas M. Werdel, July 31, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), evidence, 1950-1967 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), house precedents, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), legal documents, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), legal documents, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), legal documents, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), legal documents, 1964, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), newsclippings, 1960-1964 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), notes, n.d. (1) (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), notes, n.d. (2) (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), plaintiff's proposed jury instructions, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), reporter's partial transcript, testimony of Robert DiGiorgio and Malcolm Dungan, 1964-1965 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.),reporter's partial transcripts, testimony of Bruce W. Sanborn, Jr., Mar. 5, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Galarza v. DiGiorgio (503735, California Superior Court, San Francisco City and Co.), testimony of Tom Steed, Mar. 10, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Employment, California Weekly Farm Labor Report, 1962-1967 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Employment, correspondence, 1949-1963 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Employment, newsclippings, 1948-1965 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Employment, notes and statistics, 1946-1964 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Employment, statements and reports, 1946-1966 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Employment, displacement of U.S. workers by braceros, correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Employment, displacement of U.S. workers by braceros, notes, 1952-1959 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Employment, unemployment, 1947-1954 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Employment, unemployment, newsclippings, 1948-1961 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Farms, large-scale, 1948-1965 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Farms, small-scale, 1945-1965 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Subseries H: Geographical Locations, 1936-1966
    - Imperial Valley, affidavits, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Imperial Valley, Agricultural Crop Report, 1950, 1951, 1954-1957 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Imperial Valley, Central Labor Council, Imperial Valley Labor Council, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Imperial Valley, correspondence, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Imperial Valley, correspondence, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Imperial Valley, correspondence, 1952-1961 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Imperial Valley, crop statistics, 1949-1957 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Imperial Valley, growers' groups, 1950-1960 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Imperial Valley, miscellany, 1950-1965 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Imperial Valley, newsclippings, 1949-1951 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Imperial Valley, newsclippings, 1952-1954 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Imperial Valley, newsclippings, 1958-1971 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Imperial Valley, notes, 1950-1953 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Imperial Valley, press releases, 1951-1952 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Imperial Valley, statements and reports, 1950-1953 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Imperial Valley, strike songs, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Imperial Valley, transcripts of radio broadcasts, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Imperial Valley, Dr. Benjamin Yellen, correspondence, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Imperial Valley, Dr. Benjamin Yellen, documentation of farm worker abuses, 1958-1960 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Imperial Valley, Dr. Benjamin Yellen, newsletters, 1960-1963 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Monterey Co., Annual Crop Reports, 1957-1960 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Monterey Co., correspondence, 1951-1960 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Monterey Co., newsclippings, 1951-1963 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Monterey Co., notes, 1952-1960 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Monterey Co., pay stubs, miscellany, 1936-1966 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - San Benito Co., Annual Crop Reports, 1957-1961 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - San Benito Co., correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - San Benito Co., newsclippings, 1955-1961 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - San Benito Co., notes, 1958-1959 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - San Benito Co., "Right-to-Work" Law, 1958-1960 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - San Joaquin Co., correspondence, 1957-1962 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - San Joaquin Co., newsclippings, 1948-1961 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - San Joaquin Co., notes, 1957-1960 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - San Joaquin Co., pay stubs, 1956-1959 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - San Joaquin Co., reports, 1956-1959 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - San Joaquin Co., San Joaquin Farm Production, 1957-1959 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - San Joaquin Co., Tomato Strike (NFLU Local 300), correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - San Joaquin Co., Tomato Strike (NFLU Local 300), flyers, notes, newsclippings, 1950-1951 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Santa Clara Co., Annual Crop Reports, 1957-1960 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Santa Clara Co., correspondence, memos, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Santa Clara Co., newsclippings, 1950-1957 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Santa Clara Co., newsclippings, 1958-1960 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Santa Clara Co., notes, 1957-1960 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Stanislaus Co., Annual Crop Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Stanislaus Co., notes, newsclippings, 1957-1960 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Yolo Co., Annual Crop Report, 1957; miscellany, 1957-1960 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Yuba-Sutter Cos., affidavits, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Yuba-Sutter Cos., Annual Crop Reports, 1956-1959 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Yuba-Sutter Cos., correspondence, 1957-1959, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Yuba-Sutter Cos., newsclippings and press releases, 1956-1957 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Yuba-Sutter Cos., newsclippings and press releases, 1958-1960, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Yuba-Sutter Cos., notes, 1956-1957 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Yuba-Sutter Cos., notes, 1958-1960, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Yuba-Sutter Cos., supporting materials for notes, 1957, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Growers, correspondence, 1947-1959 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Growers, miscellany, 1947-1961 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Growers, newsclippings, 1948-1951 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Growers, newsclippings, 1952-1958 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Growers, newsclippings, 1959-1961 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Growers, notes, 1948-1960 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Growers, statements and testimony, 1958-1960 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Growers' groups, American Farm Bureau Federation, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Growers' groups, Associated Farmers of California, Inc., 1944-1963 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Growers' groups, California Farm Bureau Federation, 1950-1960 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Growers' groups, miscellany, A-P (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Growers' groups, miscellany, S-W (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Growers' groups, Northern California Growers Association, 1954-1958 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Growers' groups, Northern California Growers Association, requests for farm laborers, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Housing, Arvin-Lamont Agricultural Labor Housing Association, 1947-1948 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Housing, correspondence, 1947-1962 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Housing, evictions, 1949-1953 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Housing, miscellany, 1947-1957 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Housing, newsclippings, 1948-1964 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Housing, statements and reports, 1940-1961 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Immigration (illegal), alleged Communist infiltration, 1946-1954 (Box 50, Folder 1)